Finding Aid for University at Buffalo Music Department Oral History Recordings, 1980-1996
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
University at Buffalo Music Department Oral History Recordings, 1980-1996
Mus. Arc. 77
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
2 boxes ( 61 audiocassettes )
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library.
Oral history interviews with 24 interviewees compiled by the University at Buffalo Music Library related to local and university music history.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Administrative Information
Acquisition Information
Gift of interviewers represented in the collection.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
The collection was digitally reformatted in 2016 resulting in preservation master and service copy files that match cassette sides. The files were received on a Hard drive.
Historical Note
The collection was compiled by the University at Buffalo Music Library from multiple oral history projects with central themes of the history of music in Buffalo, and chiefly the history of the University at Buffalo Music Department. The recordings were created for projects that included the following:
Sharon G. Almquist's research for her master's thesis, A history of the State University of New York at Buffalo Music Department to 1968 (12 tapes). The text is available online at: http://hdl.handle.net/10477/2652
Alan Green's research for her master's thesis, Allen Sapp: composer, teacher, and administrator and later publication, Allen Sapp: a bio-bibliography (32 tapes)
Music faculty member James Patrick's MUS 515 class project about the history of jazz in Buffalo (3 tapes)
There is considerable overlap in the contents. For example, Allen Sapp was Chair of the Music Department and a faculty member 1961-1975. Interviews with him as the subject of a biography also contain content about the history of the Music Department. Conversations between James Coover and Carol June Bradley about the Music Library also contain information about the Music Department.
Scope and Content Note
Oral history interviews with 24 interviewees compiled by the University at Buffalo Music Library related to local and university music history. Interviewees include former faculty members of the University at Buffalo Music Department, David Fuller, Livingston Gearhart, Robert Mols, Carlo Pinto, Oswald Rantucci, Fred Ressel, Ronald Richards, Leo Smit. Other Music faculty members specifically associated with the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts include Allen Sapp, Lukas Foss, Lejaren Hiller, and Jan Williams, as well as the coordinator managing director (1965-1978), Renée Levine-Packer.
Arrangement
Arranged in one series in alphabetical order by interviewee.
Container List
- Cassettes, 1980-1996, I.; Cassette 1-61
  Arranged alphabetically by surname of interviewee.
  - Bradley, Carol June and Coover, James, 1925-2004, 1985-04-03, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Steinzor, Curt Efram Spine title: Bradley-Coover interview 4-3-85 Duration: 00:31:39 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Library History Type of tape: Maxell UD-XL II 60 mono. Side 2 is blank. (Box 1, Audiocassette 1)
    Digitized copies:
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_01_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_01_01_sc.mp3
  - Bradley, Carol June and Coover, James, 1925-2004, 1996-08-20, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: None - it is a conversation between Bradley and Coover. Spine title: Coover-Bradley 8/20/96 I Duration: 00:58:10 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Library History Type of tape: TDK D60 stereo. (Box 1, Audiocassette 2)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_02_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_02_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_02_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_02_02_sc.mp3
  - Bradley, Carol June and Coover, James, 1925-2004, 1996-08-20, 1996-08-22, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: None - it is a conversation between Bradley and Coover. Spine title: Coover-Bradley 8/20/96 II Duration: 00:43:46 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Library History Type of tape: TDK D60 stereo. (Box 1, Audiocassette 3)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_03_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_03_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_03_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_03_02_sc.mp3
  - Bradley, Carol June and Coover, James, 1925-2004, 1996-08-22, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: None - it is a conversation between Bradley and Coover. Spine title: Coover-Bradley III Duration: 00:51:21 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Library History Type of tape: TDK D60 stereo. (Box 1, Audiocassette 4)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_04_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_04_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_04_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_04_02_sc.mp3
  - Bradley, Carol June and Coover, James, 1925-2004, 1996-08-23, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: None - it is a conversation between Bradley and Coover. Spine title: Coover-Bradley 8/23/96 Duration: 00:55:32 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Library History Type of tape: TDK D60 stereo. (Box 1, Audiocassette 5)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_05_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_05_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_05_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_05_02_sc.mp3
  - Bradley, Carol June and Coover, James, 1925-2004, 1996-09-09, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: None - it is a conversation between Bradley and Coover. Spine title: Coover-Bradley V Duration: 00:47:03 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Library History Type of tape: TDK D60 stereo. (Box 1, Audiocassette 6)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_06_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_06_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_06_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_06_02_sc.mp3
  - Commanday, Robert and Dawson, Christopher, 1993-02-06, 1993-02-03, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Robert Commanday 6 Feb. 1993, Christopher Dawson 3 Feb. 1993 Duration: 01:24:46 Location of recording: San Francisco (Calif.) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: Maxell XLII 90 stereo. Side B is Dawson; Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 7)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_07_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_07_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_07_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_07_02_sc.mp3
  - Foss, Lukas, 1922-2009, 1994-03-21, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Lukas Foss, 21 March 1994 Duration: 00:06:04 Location of recording: by telephone Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK SA90 stereo. Marked Dub. Side 2 is blank. (Box 1, Audiocassette 8)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_08_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_08_01_sc.mp3
  - Foss, Lukas, 1922-2009, 1994-04-16, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Lukas Foss, 16 April 1994 Duration: 00:14:56 Location of recording: by telephone Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK D60 stereo. Marked Dub. Side 2 is blank. (Box 1, Audiocassette 9)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_09_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_09_01_sc.mp3
  - Fuller, David R., 1993-02-17, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: David Fuller 17 Feb. 1993 Duration: 00:15:35 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: Maxell XLII 90 stereo. Marked Dub. Side 2 is blank. (Box 1, Audiocassette 10)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_10_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_10_01_sc.mp3
  - Gearhart, Livingston, 1981-11-15, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Almquist, Sharon G. Spine title: Interview with Livingston Gearhart 11/15/81 Duration: 01:00:28 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Department History Type of tape: Certron 60 stereo. (Box 1, Audiocassette 11)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_11_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_11_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_11_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_11_02_sc.mp3
  - Gearhart, Livingston, 1981-11-15, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Almquist, Sharon G. Spine title: Interview with Livingston Gearhart (cont'd) 11/15/81 Duration: 01:00:20 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Department History Type of tape: Certron 60 stereo. Side 1 ends with 19 minutes of background noise. Side 2 contains only background noise. (Box 1, Audiocassette 12)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_12_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_12_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_12_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_12_02_sc.mp3
  - Gearhart, Livingston, 1984-07-26, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Bradley, Carol June Spine title: Gearhart, Livingston - 1 Duration: 00:54:51 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Department History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 mono. Marked as Preservation. (Box 1, Audiocassette 13)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_13_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_13_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_13_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_13_02_sc.mp3
  - Gearhart, Livingston, 1984-07-26, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Bradley, Carol June Spine title: Gearhart, Livingston - 2 Duration: 01:00:34 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Department History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 mono. Marked as Preservation. (Box 1, Audiocassette 14)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_14_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_14_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_14_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_14_02_sc.mp3
  - Gearhart, Livingston, 1984-07-26--1984-07-27, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Bradley, Carol June Spine title: Gearhart, Livingston - 3 Duration: 01:03:11 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Department History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 mono. Marked as Preservation. (Box 1, Audiocassette 15)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_15_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_15_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_15_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_15_02_sc.mp3
  - Gearhart, Livingston, 1984-07-27, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Bradley, Carol June Spine title: Gearhart, Livingston - 4 Duration: 00:49:59 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Department History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 mono. Marked as Preservation. (Box 1, Audiocassette 16)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_16_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_16_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_16_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_16_02_sc.mp3
  - Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994, 1981-10-21, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Almquist, Sharon G. Spine title: Interview with Dr. Lejaren Hiller 10/21/81 Duration: 00:49:11 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Department History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. (Box 1, Audiocassette 17)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_17_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_17_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_17_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_17_02_sc.mp3
  - Laster, Hal, 1994-03-22, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Hal Laster, 22 March 1994 Duration: 00:14:55 Location of recording: by telephone Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK SA90 stereo. Marked Dub. Side 2 is blank. (Box 1, Audiocassette 18)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_18_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_18_01_sc.mp3
  - Law, Rosemarie Cornelissen, 1996-05-31, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Bradley, Carol June Spine title: Law, Rosemarie Cornelissen Duration: 00:45:19 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: Buffalo Music History and Arnold Cornelissen Type of tape: TDK D60 stereo. (Box 1, Audiocassette 19)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_19_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_19_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_19_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_19_02_sc.mp3
  - Levine-Packer, Renee, 1994-03-23, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Renee Levine, 23 March 1994 Duration: 01:02:49 Location of recording: by telephone Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK D90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 20)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_20_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_20_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_20_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_20_02_sc.mp3
  - Middleton, Robert, 1920-, 1994-01-19, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Robert Middleton 19 January 1994 Duration: 00:49:07 Location of recording: Lebanon (N.H.) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK D90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 21)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_21_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_21_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_21_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_21_02_sc.mp3
  - Mols, Robert W., 1981-10-22, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Almquist, Sharon G. Spine title: Interview with Dr. Robert Mols, 10/22/81 Duration: 00:47:24 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Department History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. (Box 1, Audiocassette 22)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_22_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_22_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_22_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_22_02_sc.mp3
  - Pinto, Carlo, 1925-, 1981-10-20, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Almquist, Sharon G. Spine title: Interview with Mr. Carlo Pinto 10/20/81 Duration: 00:54:54 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Department History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. (Box 1, Audiocassette 23)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_23_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_23_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_23_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_23_02_sc.mp3
  - Rantucci, Oswald, 1981-12-16, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Almquist, Sharon G. Spine title: Interview with Mr. Oswald Rantucci, December 16, 1981 Duration: 00:30:23 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Department History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. Side 2 is blank. (Box 1, Audiocassette 24)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_24_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_24_01_sc.mp3
  - Ressel, Fred, 1983-03-04, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Almquist, Sharon G. Spine title: Interview: Fred Ressel 3/4/83 Duration: 00:25:58 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Department History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. Side 2 is blank. (Box 1, Audiocassette 25)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_25_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_25_01_sc.mp3
  - Richards, Ronald, 1981-10-28, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Almquist, Sharon G. Spine title: Interview with Ronald Richards 10/28/81 Duration: 01:00:26 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Department History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. (Box 1, Audiocassette 26)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_26_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_26_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_26_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_26_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1981-11-23, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Almquist, Sharon G. Spine title: Interview with Mr. Allen Sapp 11/23/81 Tape 1 Duration: 01:03:26 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Department History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. (Box 1, Audiocassette 27)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_27_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_27_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_27_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_27_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1981-11-23, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Almquist, Sharon G. Spine title: Interview with Mr. Allen Sapp 11/23/81 Tape 2 Duration: 00:15:54 Location of recording: Buffalo (N.Y.) Context: University at Buffalo Music Department History Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. Side 2 is blank. (Box 1, Audiocassette 28)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_28_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_28_01_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-01-05, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp (interview 5 Jan. 1991) 1/4 Duration: 01:34:18 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK AD90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 29)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_29_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_29_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_29_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_29_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-01-05, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp (interview 5 Jan. 1991) 2/4 Duration: 01:34:30 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK AD90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 30)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_30_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_30_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_30_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_30_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-01-05, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp (interview 5 Jan. 1991) 3/4 Duration: 01:34:44 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK AD90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 31)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_31_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_31_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_31_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_31_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-01-05, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp (interview 5 Jan. 1991) 4/4 Duration: 01:27:46 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK AD90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 32)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_32_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_32_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_32_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_32_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-01-12, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp (interview 12 Jan. 1991) 1/4 Duration: 01:33:07 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK AD90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 33)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_33_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_33_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_33_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_33_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-01-12, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp (interview 12 Jan. 1991) 2/4 Duration: 01:30:33 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK AD90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 34)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_34_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_34_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_34_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_34_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-01-12, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp (interview 12 Jan. 1991) 3/4 Duration: 01:34:41 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK AD90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 35)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_35_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_35_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_35_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_35_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-01-12, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp (interview 12 Jan. 1991) 4/4 Duration: 00:58:18 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK AD90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 36)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_36_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_36_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_36_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_36_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-01-16, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp (interview 16 Jan. 1991) Tape 1 of 2 Duration: 01:34:54 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK AD90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 37)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_37_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_37_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_37_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_37_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-01-16, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp (interview 16 Jan. 1991) Tape 2 of 2 Duration: 01:25:03 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK SA90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 38)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_38_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_38_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_38_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_38_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-03-25, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp 25 March 1991 Sides 1 and 2 Duration: 01:34:59 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK D90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 39)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_39_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_39_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_39_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_39_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-03-25, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp 25 March 1991 Sides 3 and 4 Duration: 01:34:32 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK D90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 40)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_40_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_40_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_40_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_40_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-03-25--1991-03-26, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp 25-26 March 1991 Sides 5-6 Duration: 01:23:10 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK D90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 41)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_41_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_41_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_41_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_41_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-03-26, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp 26 March 1991 Sides 7 and 8 Duration: 01:34:59 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK D90 stereo. Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 42)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_42_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_42_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_42_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_42_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-03-26, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp 26 March 1991 Side 9 Duration: 01:34:32 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK D90 stereo. Includes Side B (Side 10 in series); Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 43)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_43_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_43_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_43_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_43_02_sc.mp3
  - Sapp, Allen, 1922-1999, 1991-03-26, 1991-12-14, 1 audiocassette; Interviewer: Green, Alan, 1962- Spine title: Allen Sapp 26 March 1991, Side 11 of 11, 14 December 1991 Side 3 of 3 Duration: 00:03:46 Location of recording: Columbus (Ohio) Context: Allen Sapp Biography Type of tape: TDK D90 stereo. Side B is Side 3 of interview started on Tape 51; Marked Dub (Box 1, Audiocassette 44)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0077_44_01_am.wav, ubmu0077_44_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0077_44_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0077_44_02_sc.mp3